Black Teacher Archive BTA
Monroe C. Gutman Library, Harvard Graduate School of Education, Harvard University
Black Teacher Archive
1907-1973
BTA
Monroe C. Gutman Library, Harvard Graduate School of Education, Harvard University
xx Gigabytes
- National Publications
  - National Note-book Series, National Association of Teachers in Colored Schools (U.S.)
    Place of Publication
    Augusta, Georgia
    OCLC Number
    31202450
    Cataloging Note
    Also cataloged separately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155775548803941/catalog
    Issuing Body Note
    "Official publication of the National Association of Teachers in Colored Schools."
    Periodicals.
    - No.1, October 1918; bta_56402872_US_1918.; University of Oregon. Libraries
      Existence and Location of Copies
      Other digital copies of this issue
      University of Oregon. Libraries
    - No.2, August 1919; bta_56402872_US_1919.; University of Oregon. Libraries; Washington, Booker T., 1856-1915
      Physical Description of Original
      This issue is bound together v.1-5 (1930-1934) in the rare books of the North Carolina Collection at University of North Carolina Chapel Hill.
      Digital copies of this issue appear in North Carolina Library Internet Archive
  - The National Note-book Quarterly
    10508661
    Also cataloged separately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155796560403941/catalog
    - Volume I. No.4, October 1919
    - Volume II. No.1, January 1920
    - Volume II. No.2, April 1920
    - Volume II. No.3, July 1920
    - Volume II. No.4, October 1920
    - Volume III. No.2, April 1921
  - The National Note-book, National Association of Teachers in Colored Schools (U.S.)
    Augusta,Georgia
    10508664
    Also cataloged separately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155796560503941/catalog
    - Digest of the Fifteenth Annual Meeting of the National Association, October 1918; bta_10508664_US_1918.; University of Oregon. Libraries
    - Volume I. No.1, January 1919; bta_10508664_US_1919_001_001.; University of Oregon. Libraries
    - Volume I. No.2, April 1919; bta_10508664_US_1919_001_002.; University of Oregon. Libraries
    - Volume I. No.3, July 1919; bta_10508664_US_1919_001_003.; University of Oregon. Libraries
  - The National Educational Outlook Among Negroes
  - The Bulletin: Official Organ of the National Association of Teachers in Colored Schools
    Tuskegee, Alabama
    30786086
    Also cataloged seperately:http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155716110003941/catalog
    Periodicals
  - The Bulletin: Official Organ of the American Teachers Association, American Teachers Association
    Montgomery, Alabama
    30786193
    Also cataloged seperately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155801558803941/catalog
- Alabama Publications
  - The Alabama State Teachers Association Journal, 1959-1969
    44212019
    Other Finding Aids
    Also cataloged separately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155837006903941/catalog
    Fake data: This issue is bound together v.1-5 (1930-1934) in the rare books of the North Carolina Collection at University of North Carolina Chapel Hill.
  - Alabama State Teachers Association News, 1955
    44211055
    Also cataloged separately: http://id.lib.harvard.edu/alma/99155842431403941/catalog
- Arkansas Publications
  - The Bulletin of the Arkansas Teachers Association, 1962-1968; Arkansas Teachers Association
    Little Rock, Arkansas
    Conditions Governing Access
    Permission granted to Harvard Graduate School of Education to display this item for non-profit research and educational purposes. Any reuse of this item in excess of fair use or other copyright exemptions requires permission from the rights and/or repository holder.
    - Volume 30. No.3, March 1962; bta_31202450_AK_1962_030_003.; University of Arkansas, Fayetteville. Libraries
      University of Arkansas, Fayetteville. Libraries
    - Volume 30. No.4, June 1962; bta_31202450_AK_1962_030_004.; University of Arkansas, Fayetteville. Libraries
    - Volume 31. No.1, September 1962; bta_31202450_AK_1962_031_001.; University of Arkansas, Fayetteville. Libraries
    - Volume 31. No.2, December 1962; bta_31202450_AK_1962_031_002.; University of Arkansas, Fayetteville. Libraries